questions = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "Hi, I'm Chandler. I make jokes when I'm uncomfortable",
        "answer" : "Friends"
    },

    2 : {
        "question" : "Gosh Amy. I'm sensing a little hostility. Is it maybe because like Sheldon's work your sex life is also theoretical?",
        "answer" : "The Big Bang Theory"        
    },

    3 : {
        "question" : "No need to seize the last word Lord Baelish. I'll assume it was something clever",
        "answer" : "Game of Thrones"
    },

    4 : {
        "question" : "Jerry, just remeber, it,s not a lie if you believe it",
         "answer" : "Seinfeld"
    },

    5 : {
        "question" : "You either run from things or you face them, Mr. White.",
        "answer" : "Breaking Bad"
    },
    
    6 : {
        "question" : "Oh my God! They killed Kenny",
        "answer" : "South Park"
    },

    7 : {
        "question" : "Winter is coming...",
        "answer" : "Game of Thrones"
    },

    8 : {
        "question" : "Luke, don't give in to the hate. That leads to the dark side",
        "answer" : "Star Wars"
    }
}


level_two = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "Theodore Bagwell, Micheal Scofeild",
        "answer" : "prison break"
    },

    2 : {
        "question" : "Ofwarren, Serena Joy, Ofglen",
        "answer" : "the handmaid's tale"        
    },

    3 : {
        "question" : "Jon Snow, Samwell Tarly",
        "answer" : "Game of Thrones"
    },

    4 : {
        "question" : "Phillip Banks, Will Smith",
         "answer" : "the fresh prince of belair"
    },

    5 : {
        "question" : "Micheal Kelso, Laurie Forman, Steven Hyde",
        "answer" : "that 70s show"
    },
    
    6 : {
        "question" : "Leonard Hofstadter, Bernadette Rostenkowski",
        "answer" : "the big bang theory"
    },

    7 : {
        "question" : "Monica Geller, Joey Tribiani, Phoebe Buffay",
        "answer" : "Friends"
    },

    8 : {
        "question" : "Don Draper, Peggy Olson",
        "answer" : "mad men"
    }
}


level_three = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "Hi, I'm Chandler. I make jokes when I'm uncomfortable",
        "answer" : "Friends"
    },

    2 : {
        "question" : "Gosh Amy. I'm sensing a little hostility. Is it maybe because like Sheldon's work your sex life is also theoretical?",
        "answer" : "The Big Bang Theory"        
    },

    3 : {
        "question" : "No need to seize the last word Lord Baelish. I'll assume it was something clever",
        "answer" : "Game of Thrones"
    },

    4 : {
        "question" : "Jerry, just remeber, it,s not a lie if you believe it",
         "answer" : "Seinfeld"
    },

    5 : {
        "question" : "You either run from things or you face them, Mr. White.",
        "answer" : "Breaking Bad"
    },
    
    6 : {
        "question" : "Oh my God! They killed Kenny",
        "answer" : "South Park"
    },

    7 : {
        "question" : "Winter is coming...",
        "answer" : "Game of Thrones"
    },

    8 : {
        "question" : "Luke, don't give in to the hate. That leads to the dark side",
        "answer" : "Star Wars"
    }
}
